question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Furby was released in 1998.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The sum of all the numbers on a roulette wheel is 666.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The British organisation CAMRA stands for The Campaign for Real Ale.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The French word for &quot;glass&quot; is &quot;glace&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "&quot;Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo.&quot; is a grammatically correct sentence.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "A pencil&#039;s lead is typically made from graphite, not lead",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    }
]
